RG 062:083, Town of Middletown
Connecticut State Library
Town of Middletown records
1860-1949
Connecticut State Library
Middletown (Conn.)
49 cubic feet
Tax records for the town of Middletown.
RG062_083
T000255
Historical Note
The town of Middletown was incorporated on September 11, 1651 and named in November 1653. The city was incorporated in 1784. The town and city consolidated in 1923.
Scope and Content
Tax records for the town of Middletown.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Tax assessment -- Connecticut -- Middletown -- Registers; Taxation -- Connecticut -- Middletown -- Registers; Local taxation -- Connecticut -- Middletown -- Registers; Property tax -- Connecticut -- Middletown -- Registers
Places:
Middletown (Conn.) -- Records and corresopndence
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Records, 1860-1949
  - Tax abstracts
    Tax abstracts for 1886 to 1949 are not boxed.
    - Westfield, Newfield, Staddle Hill, 1860 (Box Box 1)
    - South Farms, Maromas, 1860 (Box Box 1)
    - Middlefield, Long Hill, 1860 (Box Box 1)
    - City Limits, 1860 (Box Box 1)
    - Westfield, Newfield, Staddle Hill, 1861 (Box Box 2)
    - South Farms, Maromas, 1861 (Box Box 2)
    - Middlefield, Long Hill, 1861 (Box Box 2)
    - City Limits, 1861 (Box Box 2)
    - Westfield, Newfield, Staddle Hill, 1862 (Box Box 3)
    - South Farms, Maromas, 1862 (Box Box 3)
    - Middlefield, Long Hill, 1862 (Box Box 3)
    - City District, 1862 (Box Box 3)
    - Westfield, Newfield, Staddle Hill, 1863 (Box Box 4)
    - South Farms, Maromas, 1863 (Box Box 4)
    - Middlefield, Long Hill, 1863 (Box Box 4)
    - City District, 1863 (Box Box 4)
    - Westfield, Newfield, Staddle Hill, 1864 (Box Box 4)
    - South Farms, Maromas, 1864 (Box Box 4)
    - Middlefield, Long Hill, 1864 (Box Box 4)
    - Untitled, 1865 (Box Box 5)
    - Westfield, Newfield, Staddle Hill, 1865 (Box Box 5)
    - South Farms, Maromas, 1865 (Box Box 5)
    - Middlefield, Long Hill, 1865 (Box Box 5)
    - City District, 1865 (Box Box 5)
    - Westfield, Newfield, Staddle Hill, Long Hill, 1866 (Box Box 5)
    - South Farms, Maromas, 1866 (Box Box 5)
    - City District, 1866 (Box Box 5)
    - Westfield, Newfield, Staddle Hill, Long Hill, 1867 (Box Box 6)
    - South Farms, Maromas, 1867 (Box Box 6)
    - City District, 1867-1868 (Box Box 6)
    - Westfield, Newfield, Staddle Hill, Long Hill, 1868 (Box Box 7)
    - South Farms, Maromas, 1868 (Box Box 7)
    - Untitled, 1869 (Box Box 7)
    - Untitled, 1870 (Box Box 8)
    - Westfield, Newfield, Staddle Hill, Long Hill (1), 1870 (Box Box 8)
    - Westfield, Newfield, Staddle Hill, Long Hill (2), 1870 (Box Box 8)
    - City District, 1870 (Box Box 8)
    - Westfield, Newfield, Staddle Hill, Long Hill, 1871 (Box Box 9)
    - South Farms, Maromas, 1871 (Box Box 9)
    - City District, 1871 (Box Box 9)
    - Westfield, Newfield, Staddle Hill, Long Hill, 1872 (Box Box 9)
    - Untitled, 1872 (Box Box 9)
    - City District, 1872 (Box Box 9)
    - Westfield, Newfield, Staddle Hill, Long Hill, 1873 (Box Box 10)
    - South Farms, Maromas, 1873 (Box Box 10)
    - City District, 1873 (Box Box 10)
    - Westfield, Newfield, Staddle Hill, Long Hill, 1874 (Box Box 10)
    - South Farms, Maromas, 1874 (Box Box 10)
    - City District, 1874 (Box Box 10)
    - Westfield, Newfield, Staddle Hill, Long Hill, 1875 (Box Box 11)
    - South Farms, Maromas, 1875 (Box Box 11)
    - City District, 1875 (Box Box 11)
    - Westfield, Newfield, Staddle Hill, Long Hill, 1876 (Box Box 12)
    - South Farms, Maromas, 1876 (Box Box 12)
    - City District, 1876 (Box Box 12)
    - Westfield, Newfield, Staddle Hill, Long Hill, 1877 (Box Box 13)
    - South Farms, Maromas, 1877 (Box Box 13)
    - City District, 1877 (Box Box 13)
    - Westfield, Newfield, Staddle Hill, Long Hill, 1878 (Box Box 14)
    - South Farms, Maromas, 1878 (Box Box 14)
    - City District, 1878 (Box Box 14)
    - Westfield, Newfield, Staddle Hill, Long Hill, 1879 (Box Box 15)
    - South Farms, Maromas, 1879 (Box Box 15)
    - City District, 1879 (Box Box 15)
    - City Grand List, 1880 (Box Box 16)
    - Westfield, Newfield, Staddle Hill, Long Hill, 1880 (Box Box 16)
    - South Farms, Maromas, 1880 (Box Box 16)
    - City District, 1880 (Box Box 16)
    - Westfield, Newfield, Staddle Hill, Long Hill, 1881 (Box Box 17)
    - South Farms, Maromas, 1881 (Box Box 17)
    - City District, 1881 (Box Box 17)
    - Westfield, Newfield, Staddle Hill, Long Hill, 1882 (Box Box 18)
    - South Farms, Maromas, 1882 (Box Box 18)
    - City District, 1882 (Box Box 18)
    - Westfield, Newfield, Staddle Hill, Long Hill, 1883 (Box Box 19)
    - South Farms, Maromas, 1883 (Box Box 19)
    - City District, 1883 (Box Box 19)
    - Westfield, Newfield, Staddle Hill, Long Hill, 1884 (Box Box 20)
    - South Farms, Maromas, 1884 (Box Box 20)
    - Westfield, Newfield, Staddle Hill, Long Hill, 1885 (Box Box 21)
    - South Farms, Maromas, 1885 (Box Box 21)
    - City District, 1885 (Box Box 21)
    - Town of Middletown, 1886; 1 volume
    - Town of Middletown, 1887; 1 volume
    - Town of Middletown, 1888; 1 volume
    - City of Middletown, 1888; 1 volume
    - Town of Middletown, 1889; 1 volume
    - City of Middletown, 1889; 1 volume
    - Town of Middletown, 1890; 1 volume
    - Ciy of Middletown, 1890; 1 volume
    - Town of Middletown, 1891; 1 volume
    - City of Middletown, 1891; 1 volume
    - Town of Middletown, 1892; 1 volume
    - City of Middletown, 1892; 1 volume
    - Durant School District, 1892; 1 volume
    - Town of Middletown, 1893; 1 volume
    - City of Middletown, 1893; 1 volume
    - Town of Middletown, 1894; 1 volume
    - Durant School District, 1894; 1 volume
    - Town of Middletown, 1895; 1 volume
    - Durant School District, 1895-1896; 1 volume
    - Town of Middletown, 1896; 1 volume
    - Town of Middletown, 1897; 1 volume
    - Town of Middletown, 1898; 1 volume
    - Durant School District, 1898-1899; 1 volume
    - Town of Middletown, 1899; 1 volume
    - Town of Middletown, 1900; 1 volume
    - Town of Middletown, 1901; 1 volume
    - Farm Hill School District, 1901; 1 volume
    - Town of Middletown, 1902; 1 volume
    - Town of Middletown, 1903; 1 volume
    - Town of Middletown, 1904; 1 volume
    - Durant School District, 1904; 1 volume
    - Farm Hill School District, 1904; 1 volume
    - Town of Middletown, 1905; 1 volume
    - Town of Middletown, 1906; 1 volume
    - Town of Middletown, 1907; 1 volume
    - Town of Middletown, 1908; 1 volume
    - Farm Hill School District, 1908; 1 volume
    - Town of Middletown, 1909; 1 volume
    - Westfield Consolidated School District, 1909; 1 volume
    - North Staddle Hill School District, 1909; 1 volume
    - Farm Hill School District, 1909; 1 volume
    - Town of Middletown, 1910; 1 volume
    - South Staddle Hill School District, 1910; 1 volume
    - Town of Middletown, 1911; 1 volume
    - East Long Hill School District, 1911; 1 volume
    - Town of Middletown, 1912; 1 volume
    - West Long Hill School District, 1912; 1 volume
    - Miller's Farms School District, 1912; 1 volume
    - Town of Middletown, 1913; 1 volume
    - Miller's Farms School District, 1913; 1 volume
    - Town of Middletown, 1914; 1 volume
    - Miller's Farms School District, 1914; 1 volume
    - Town of Middletown, 1915; 1 volume
    - Town of Middletown, 1916; 1 volume
    - Town of Middletown, 1917; 1 volume
    - Town of Middletown, 1918; 1 volume
    - Town of Middletown, 1919; 1 volume
    - Town of Middletown, 1920; 1 volume
    - Town of Middletown, 1921; 1 volume
    - Town of Middletown, 1922; 1 volume
    - Town of Middletown, 1923; 1 volume
    - Town of Middletown, 1924; 1 volume
    - City of Middletown, 1925; 1 volume
    - City of Middletown, 1926; 1 volume
    - City of Middletown, 1927; 1 volume
    - City of Middletown, 1928; 1 volume
    - City of Middletown, 1929; 1 volume
    - City of Middletown, 1930; 1 volume
    - City of Middletown, 1931; 1 volume
    - City of Middletown, 1932; 1 volume
    - City of Middletown, 1933; 1 volume
    - City of Middletown, 1934; 1 volume
    - City of Middletown, 1935; 1 volume
    - City of Middletown, 1936; 1 volume
    - City of Middletown, 1937; 1 volume
    - City of Middletown, 1938; 1 volume
    - City of Middletown, 1939; 1 volume
    - City of Middletown, 1940; 1 volume
    - City of Middletown, 1941; 1 volume
    - City of Middletown, 1942; 1 volume
    - City of Middletown, 1943; 1 volume
    - City of Middletown, 1944; 1 volume
    - City of Middletown, 1945; 1 volume
    - City of Middletown, 1946; 1 volume
    - City of Middletown, 1947; 1 volume
    - City of Middletown, 1948; 1 volume
    - City of Middletown, 1949; 1 volume